Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration, 1984-2023; 1; 2.2 cubic ft.; 3.39 GB
  - QuickBooks Balance Sheet, 2014 December 31
  - QuickBooks Monthly Income & Expense Report, 2015-2023
  - QuickBooks Statement of Financial Position, 2015-2023
  - QuickBooks Year to Date Income & Expense Report, 2015-2023
  - "Race Disparities in Virginia Executions" Graphic, 1900-1969; 1970; 2020 September 15
  - Receipts, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Registration Form and Letters with Virginia Commonwealth Office of Charitable & Regulatroy Programs, 2012; 2014-2023 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Registration for VADP at Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission, 2007 November 1
  - Renny Cushing Head Shot, 2019 August 15
  - Renny Cushing Head Shot, Small, 2019 August 15
  - Request Funds from Blessed Sacrament in Alexandria, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from Church of the Nativity, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from Church of the Redeemer in Mechanicsville, 2018 April 6
  - Request Funds from Church of the Redeemer in Mechanicsville, 2019 April 4
  - Request Funds from Church of the Redeemer in Mechanicsville, 2020 July 1
  - Request Funds from Goose Creek Friends Meeting, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from Richmond Friends Meeting, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from Six Churches Who Donated in 2018, 2019 October 19; 2019 October 25
  - Request Funds from St. Bridgets in Richmond, Virginia, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from St. Edwards in Richmond, Virginia, 2019 April 10
  - Request Funds from St. paul's in Richmond, Virginia, 2019 April 10
  - Requests for Information, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rescheduled VADP Awards Luncheon Flyer, 2019 January 24; 2019 March 24
  - Richmond Area VADP Donors Awards Luncheon Flyers, 2016 August 31
  - ROSMY Financial Statements, 2014 May 15
  - Ryan Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2009 March 23
  - Salsa Database Exported Donations with Email Addresses, 2015 March 25; 2011-2015
  - Scan of Previous VADP Bylaws & Articles, 2007 September 21
  - Scott Collum, Ph.D. Full Biography, 2012 May 22
  - Scott Vollum Biography, Undated
  - Scott Vollum Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2009 April 6
  - Scott Vollum, Ph.D. Short Biography, Undated
  - Screenshot from Abolition University Session on Capital Defense Attorneys, 2020 June 18
  - Screenshot from Abolition University Session on Victim Family Members, 2020 May 27; 2020 May 28
  - Screenshot from Insider Update on Virginia Podboy, 2020 April 17; 2020 April 22
  - Screenshot of Board Virtual Toast to Abolition, 2021 February 5
  - Screenshot of Bryan Stevenson Video, 2021 July 1
  - Screenshot of Delegate Chris Hurst on Senate Abolition Bill, 2021 February 22
  - Screenshot of Delegate Jay Jones on Abolition Bill, 2021 February 5; 2021 May 27
  - Screenshot of Senator at Kaine Event, 2020 July 30; 2020 July 31
  - Screenshot of VADP Virtual Celebration, 2021 March 24
  - Screenshot of Virtual Awards Rachel Sutphin, 2020 October 24; 2020 October 21
  - Senate District 9 Constituents, User Report, 2010 February 17
  - Senate District 16 Constituents, 2010 February 17
  - Senate District 18 Constituents, User Report, 2010 February 17
  - Senate District 34, User Report, 2010 February 17
  - Senate District 35 Constituents, User Report, 2010 February 17
  - Senate District 36 Constituents, User Report, 2010 February 17
  - Senator Cuccinelli Notes, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Senator Tim Kaine VADP Certification Letter for Senate Ethics, Signed, 2020 May 8
  - Senator Tim Kaine VADP Certification Letter for Senate Ethics, Template, 2020 May 8
  - Shepard's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP, 2016 April 22
  - Shepard's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP, 2017 April 25
  - Shepard's Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP, 2018 March 26
  - Shepard's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP, 2019 April 4
  - Shepard's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP, 2020 April 3
  - Shepherd's Gate Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP Attachment D- IRS 501(c)(3) Letter, 2018 March 26; 2014 August 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP, 2020 April 3
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment A- Other Information, 2016 April 22
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment B- Budget, 2016 April 22
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment C- Statement of Purpose, 2016 April 22
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment D- Board of Directors List, 2016 April 22; 2015 December 3
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment E- IRS 501(c)(3) Letter, 2016 April 22; 2014 August 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2016 VADP Attachment F- 2015 Annual Financial Statement, 2016 April 22; 2016 January 3; 2015 January-2015 December
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment A- Other Information, 2017 April 25
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment B- Budget, 2017 April 25
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment C- Statement of Purpose, 2017 April 25
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment D- Board of Directors List, 2017 April 25; 2017 February 2
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment E- IRS 501(c)(3) Letter, 2017 April 25; 2014 August 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2017 VADP Attachment F-2016 Annual Financial Statement, 2017 April 25; 2017 January 17; 2016 January-2016 December
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP Attachment A- Budget, 2018 March 26
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP Attachment B- Statement of Purpose, 2018 March 26
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP Attachment C- Board of Directors List, 2018 March 26; 2018 March 13
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2018 VADP Attachment E- 2017 Annual Financial Statement, 2018 March 26; 2018 January 8; 2017 January-2017 December
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP Attachment A- Budget, 2019 April 4; 2018 November 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP Attachment B- Statement of Purpose, 2019 April 4
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP Attachment C- Board of Directors, 2019 April 4; 2019 March 4
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP Attachment D- IRS 501(c)(3) Letter, 2019 April 4; 2014 August 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2019 VADP Attachment E- 2019 Annual Financial Statement, 2019 April 4; 2019 January 3; 2018 January-2018 December
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP Attachment A- Budget, 2020 April 3; 2020 January 4
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP Attachment B- Statement of Purpose, 2019 April 4
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP Attachment C- Board of Directors List, 2020 April 3; 2020 March 2
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP Attachment D- IRS 501(c)(3) Letter, 2019 April 4; 2014 August 12
  - Shepherd's Gate Grant Application 2020 VADP Attachment E- 2019 Annual Financial Statement, 2020 January 2; 2019 January-2020 December
  - Shopping List for VADP Board Meetings, 2016 September 16
  - Short Term Fundraiser List with Assignments, 2013 August 9
  - Short Term Fundraiser Thank You List, 2013 September 13
  - Short Term Fundraising Letter, 2013 August 7
  - Short Term Fundraising Letter, Select Donors, 2013 August 5
  - Short Term Fundraising Thank You Letter, 2013 September 13
  - Short-Term Fundraiser List, 2013 August 6
  - Short-Term Fundraiser List with Assignments, 2013 August 9
  - Short-Term Fundraiser Results, 2013 August 20
  - Short-Term Fundraising Letter, Former Board Members, 2013 August 15
  - Short-Term Fundraising Letter, Former Board Members, 2 Week Push, 2013 August 15
  - Signed Bylaws for VADP, Signed by Mitchell, 2013 January 16; 2013 February 5
  - Sister Helen Prejean, 2005
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Fund Accountability Report, 2018 September 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Fund, VADP Application, Final, 2019 January; 2018 December 14
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, 2016 July; 2016 July 18
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application References, 2016 July; 2016 July 18
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application References, 2017 January; 2016 December 22
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application References, 2018 January; 2017 December 21
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application References, 2019 January
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Cover Letter, 2017 January; 2016 December 22
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Cover Letter, 2018 January; 2017 December 20
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Draft, 2016 July; 2016 July 18
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Draft 2, 2017 January; 2016 November 2
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Draft 3, 2017 January; 2016 November 29
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Final, 2017 January; 2016 December 22
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Application, Final, 2018 January; 2017 December 21
  - The Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Cover Sheet, 2016 July; 2016 July 18
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, 2017-2020 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, Semi-Annual Report, Draft, 2017 September 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, Semi-Annual Report, Final, 2017 September 22; 2017 September 12
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report, 2020 March 9
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report, 2018 March 22; 2018 March 12
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report Draft 2, 2018 March 22; 2018 March 9
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report Draft 3, 2018 March 22; 2018 March 9
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report, Draft, 2019 March 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report, Signed, 2019 March 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Final Report, Signed, 2020 March 9
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Semi-Annual Report, 2019 September 11
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Semi-Annual Report, Draft, 2018 September 22; 2018 September 10
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Semi-Annual Report, Draft, 2019 September 11
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Semi-Annual Report, Final, 2018 September 22; 2018 September 11
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Ministry Grant Fund, VADP Semi-Annual Report, Final Signed, 2019 September 11
  - Sisters of Bon Secours Sisters Ministry Grant Fund, 2020 March 9; 2020 March 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA Rejection Letter for Ministry Grant Fund, 2016 August 15
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Acceptance Letter from VADP, 2017 March 1; 2017 February 23
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Accpetance Letter from VADP, 2018 February 23; 2018 February 22
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Accpetance Letter from VADP, 2019 February 19
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Award Letter, 2017 February 23; 2017 February 28
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Award Letter, 2018 February 13; 2018 February 23
  - Sisters of Bon Secours USA, Grant Award Letter, 2019 February 12; 2019 February 19
  - Sisters of Bon Secours, USA, Ministry Grant Application Form VADP Application Draft 1, 2019 January; 2018 December 6
  - Sisters of Bon Secours, USA, Ministry Grant Application Form VADP Application Draft 2, 2019 January; 2018 December 12
  - Sisters of Bon Secours, USA, Ministry Grant Application Form VADP Application Final, 2019 January; 2018 December 12
  - Slide 1 for 2020-21 Annual Report, Final, 2020-2021
  - Slide 2 for 2020 Abolition History, Final
  - Slide of "VADP Established in 1991", 2021 August 18
  - Slide of 1991 VADP Founding, 2021 August 18
  - Slide of 2022 Virginia General Assembly Review, 2021 January 12
  - Slide of Virginia Exonerees, 2019 December; 2020 August 18
  - Slide on Capital Defense Attorneys, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Earl Washington Exoneration, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Executions by U.S. Regions, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Innocence, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Modern Virginia Executions Map, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Murder Victims Family Members, 2017; 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Murder Victims Family Members, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on State Execution Chart, Since 1608, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on State Execution Chart, Since 1976, 2021 August 18; 2019 September 1
  - Slide on Virginia Execution Methods, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Virginia Exonerees, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Virginia Localities with 100 Years Ago, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Virginia Localities with No Execution, 2021 August 18
  - Slide on Virginia Lynchings, 2021 August 18
  - Small Business Administration COVID-19 Economic Injury Disaster Loan Application, Completed, 2020 September 30
  - Small Business Administration COVID-19 Economic Injury Disaster Loan Application, Receipt Page, 2020 September 30
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection, 2020 November 30
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Program Application Form, Computer Version, 2020 April 2
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Program Borrower Application Form, Completed by Hand, 2020 April 4
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Program Payroll Analysis Form, 2020 April 7
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Programs Loan Forgiveness Calculation Form, Completed by Hand, 2020 June 16
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Programs Loan Forgiveness Calculation Form, Completed by Hand, Revised, 2020 July 29
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Programs Loan Forgiveness Calculation Form, Completed Online, 2020 April 17
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection Programs Loans (PPP) FAQs, 2020 April 8
  - Small Business Administration Paycheck Protection VCC Fogiveness Documentation Checklist, 2020 August 31
  - Small Business Adminstration Paycheck Protection Program Borrower Application Form, Completed by Hand, 2020 July 29
  - Sonjia Smith Handwritten Note Asking for Meeting, 2017 November 17
  - Special Appeal to Biggest Major Donors, 2018 June; 2018 June 18
  - Special Events Insurance Application, Ball-Martin Insurance Agency, Inc., 2021 September 1; 2021 November 21
  - Special Events Insurance Policy for VADP Luncheon by USLI, 2021 November 8
  - Special Events Insurance Policy for VADP Luncheon by USLI- Copy for DoubleTree Hotel, 2021 September 1; 2021 November 21-2021 November 23
  - Spreadsheet of Donations to VADP, 2011-2012
  - State Corporation Commission, VADP Education Fund, 2000; 2002; 2003; 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - St Marys Catholic Church Human Concerns Donation Check, 2015 September 10; 2015 September 1
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2015 Application- VADP, 2015 June 4
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2016 Application- VADP, 2016 June 9
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2017 Application- VADP, 2017 July 5
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2018 Application Form, 2018 June 1
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2018 Application- VADP, 2018 June 5
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2019 Application- VADP, 2019 June 7
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2020 Application- VADP, 2020 June 4
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2021 Application Form, 2021 June 3
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2021 Application- VADP, 2021 June 8
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2022 Application- VADP, 2022 June 7
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2023 Application Form, 2023 June 6
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund 2023 Application- VADP, 2023 June 6
  - St Marys Human Concerns Endowment Fund Application- VADP, 2020 June 4
  - State Corporation Commission Certificate Amendment, 2013 December 19
  - Strategic Planning Meeting, 2009 May; 2008; 2010 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Statewide Community Organization Plan, 2006; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Statewide Event Invitation Letter from Tom Gallagher to Guests, 2015 September 8
  - Statewide Event Invitation List of Donor Faith Communities Recipient List, 2015 October 10
  - Statewide Event Invitation List to Donor Faith Communities Labels, 2015 October 10
  - Statewide Event Invitation Lists from Tom Gallagher & Steve Northup, 2015 October 10; 2015 August 7
  - Statewide Event Invitation Lists from Tom Gallagher & Steve Northup, 2015 October 10; 2015 August 6
  - Statewide Event Letter to Donor Faith Communities, 2015 September 1
  - Statewide Event Planning Team Budget, 2015 June 2
  - Statewide Event Planning Team Budget, 2015 June 5
  - Statewide Event Planning Team Conference Call Notes, 2015 June 2
  - Steve Northup Biography, Undated
  - Steve Northup Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2007 October 11
  - Steve Northup Signature, 2010 December 14
  - Strategic Planning Overview, 2012 September 18
  - Students Against the Death Penalty, 2004; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Suddes Group VADP Client Discovery Response, 2016 July 15
  - Summary from VADP Strategic Planning Meeting, 2011 May 6-2011 May 7; 2011 June 2
  - Table of Contents for Manual, 2011 May 27
  - Table of Contents for Manual, 2011 May 27
  - Tactic Sheet, 2008 November 5
  - Tax Documents 990-EZ Form, 2001-2021 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Teleconference Notes and Materials, 1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - "The ten most important things you can know about fundraising" Tip Sheet, 2004 January-2004 February
  - Test Download of Mail Appeal with Money, 2018 July 17
  - Test Download of Mail Appeal with Money, 2018 July 18
  - Thank you Letter for Board Service from Executive Director, 2020 August 27
  - Thank You Letter to Thomas Gallagher Regarding Purchase of Eight Tickets, 2015 September 10
  - Theresa Dunleavy Letter to Tidewater Parishes, 2018 July; 2017 July 18; 2018 July 20
  - Ticket Purchase by Thomas Gallagher, 2015 September 7
  - Tides Advocacy Fund Report: VADP, 2009 October 2; 2011 March 16
  - Tides Foundation Grant, 2006; 2008; 2010 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Tides Foundation VADP Cover Sheet and Proposal Narrative, 2009 May 1
  - Tides Foundation/Tides Advocacy Fund VADP Application, 2010
  - Tides goals, 2008 September 28
  - "To do/Catch All" Notes, 2008 October 1
  - Total Donor List BSD, 2015 June 24
  - "Tyson" Biography, Undated
  - Unidenitified Charts and Graphs, 2012 September 12
  - Unidentified List of Funraising Names, 2009 May 13
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Arlington Virginia Upper Level Map, 2019 July 9
  - United Flight Boarding Passes, Michael Stone, 2023 June 24
  - Univeristy of Richmond Alcohol Options, 2018-2019; 2021 May 17
  - University of Richmond - Catering Boxed Meal Menu, 2021 May 17
  - University of Richmond - Dinner Options, 2021 May 24
  - University of Richmond - Lunch Options, 2021 May 24
  - University of Richmond Events Conferences & Support Services, 2021 November 21; 2021 May 17
  - University of Richmond Jepson Alumni Center Rental Information and Guidelines, 2021 May 17
  - Updated Addresses for VADP database, 2018 March 1; 2018 March 8
  - Updated VADP Fundraising Work Plan, 2009 April 21
  - User Defined Report for Deeds 25 Constituents, 2010 February 17
  - User Defined Report, Devine, 2009 December 8
  - User Defined Report, District 21 Constituents, 2010 February 17
  - UVA Vendor Registration Confirmation, 2016 March 3
  - VA Coalition- CHD Proposal, 1985 March 3; 1985 October 7; 1985 October 22; 1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - VA Department of Taxation- 2014 Withholding Taxes & Penalty Due, 2015 July 12
  - VA Department of Taxation Change of Address Form Completed, 2015 June 29
  - VA Department of Taxation Letter Regarding Monthly Tax Witholding Returns, 2015 November 18
  - VA Lobbyist Principal Signature Waiver Form, 2016 June 23
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Annual Renewal, 2020
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Annual Renewal, 2021
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Annual Renewal, 2022
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Annual Renewal, 2023
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Annual Renewal, Revised Draft, 2019
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Compliance Letter, 2017 June 7
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Corrections to Initial Registration Form 102, 2015 April 29
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Corrections to Registration Form 102, 2021 April 16
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Addendum Requested, 2021 April 2
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, 2015 May 15
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, 2016 May 15
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, 2017 April 21
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, 2018
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal Payment, 2017 April 21
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Computer Adam Signature, 2021 March 10
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Draft, 2016 May 15
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Draft, 2018
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Draft, 2019
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Handwritten Adam Signature, 2021 April 15
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Signature Page, 2021
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Annual Renewal, Signature Page, 2022 March 29
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 Initial Registration, 2014 October 14
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Form 102 State Corrections, 2021
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Registration Letter, 2015 June 1
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Remittance Form 102, Draft, 2021
  - VA Office of Charitable and Regulatory Programs Request for VADP Documents Letter, 2016 August 12
  - VADP, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - VADP 8th Amendment Project- Budget Template, 2020; 2019 August 20
  - VADP 8th Amendment Project- Cover Letter, 2019 August 20
  - VADP 8th Amendment Project- Organization/Project Budget Template, 2020; 2019 August 20
  - VADP 8th Amendment Project- Proposal Information, 2019 August 20
  - VADP 10th Anniversary Banquet, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - VADP 10th Anniversary Banquet Preparation, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - VADP 500 Plus Donors, All Time, 2012 September 11
  - VADP 990 Tax Return, 2009; 2010 May 26
  - VADP 1999 Annual Conference (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - VADP 2008 Exempt Organization Return, Form 990-EZ, 2009 July 8
  - VADP 2008 Projected Budget, 2008 September
  - VADP 2009 Annual 990 Tax Return, 2010 May 26
  - VADP 2009 Annual Report, 2009 April 15
  - VADP 2011-2012 Development Plan, Draft, 2012 April 26
  - VADP 2012 Balance Sheet, 2015 July 30; 2012 December 31
  - VADP 2012 Development Plan, Draft, 2011-2012; 2012 April 25
  - VADP 2012 Income Expenses, 2015 July 30
  - VADP 2013 Balance Sheet, 2015 July 30; 2013 December 31
  - VADP 2013 Income Expenses, 2015 July 30
  - VADP 2015 Development Action Plan, 2015 July 17; 2015 July 24
  - VADP 2015 Development Action Plan, 2015 September 10; 2015 September 18
  - VADP 2015 Development Action Plan Sheet, 2015 September 10
  - VADP 2015 Development Action Plan, Draft, 2015 July 24